But I don't want to give up!
In the hole in the bottom of my dreams?
I can't believe
in my hope.
I will be able to find this way!
I will change the world.
Thank you.
Fighting God
Any who met Giorno's mother would call
her a vision of unblemished beauty.
Motherhood, however, was a struggle.
After Giorno's birth, she
and her son lived in Japan,
where she left Giorno
at home in favor of a
nightlife of glamour and
bacchanalian revelry.
You're really gonna leave
him there by himself?
Isn't he, like, two?
Oh, he'll be fine.
There's no way I'm gonna let some kid
take away my freedom, and that's that.
Countless nights, Giorno
awoke to a vacant room.
The fear and desperation that terrorized
his soul must have been immeasurable.
The boy knew crying was futile,
so all he could do was tremble.
When Giorno was four, his
mother married an Italian man.
It was the marriage that would
make Giorno an Italian citizen.
Pardon me, but...
Now why are you hiding over here?
Come on, Haruno.
Come with daddy so he
can take the pictures.
Mommy's waiting for you, too.
But when his wife was away from the
house, or she wasn't paying attention...
You're always trying to skulk
around corners and spy on me!
You annoying little brat!
Giorno suffered.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Oh, the bread.
Take it, you're a depressing
little shit, you know that?
Giorno was a constant
observer of human expression,
thanks to the very man
who stood before him.
But Giorno had also become an easy mark
for the frustrated youth roaming the city.
Whoa, what's with you, Giorno?
Why are you tripping over
your own feet like some klutz?
Hey you punks move your
asses and get home!
Fine, let's beat it.
Yeah, go back to your country you!
Japanese freak.
He never even fights back.
What a weirdo.
The boy soon saw himself
as the scum of the earth.
He worried it would only be a
matter of time before he became
another crooked member of the
Neapolitan underbelly plaguing his city.
But little did Giorno
know a single incident
was He's about to forever change his life.
Merda!
Where'd that bastard go?
Grab him before he slips away!
He won't get far with those injuries.
Could he have hidden someone's house?
Make sure you check the ground.
He's gotta be bleeding out.
You go straight.
We'll check out this way.
Rigazzo!
You haven't seen an injured
guy around here, have you?
He's pretty tall and has black hair.
I saw him go that way. Over there?
Well, he won't be moving
very fast in his condition.
Let's move!
Fear had no grip on the boy.
The only thought Giorno
had when he saw the
helpless man was that he
was friendless and alone,
just like him.
Come on! Yeah!
In a strange turn of luck, A patch of
weed sprung up and obscured the man.
Unbeknownst to Giorno, it was a
consequence of his golden wind ability.
At the time,
he had no awareness of the power and
activated the ability on pure instinct.
Two months later...
You saved my life back there.
I won't forget that.
Before long, the beatings Giorno received
from his stepfather ceased altogether.
Damn it!
Why does he care about this kid?
Sit with us, Giorno!
The bullies no longer pestered him.
The man was a mafioso.
Eccoti!
Wow, two scoops.
I think you gave me too much.
The Chocolato is my special treat.
Thank you.
Of course, kid.
I owe a heck of a lot to that guy.
The man continued to watch
over him from a quiet distance.
Being an observer of human expression,
Giorno could tell he was paying
his respects not to a lowly child,
but to his fellow man.
Giorno learned a basic skill
from this silent stranger,
one his parents never
managed to teach him.
The ability to trust.
What was that? A gunshot?
We should just stay out of it.
Talk about bad luck.
Scusi!
Huh, what is it?
The man acted as if
Giorno wasn't even there,
determined to keep him far away
from the grips of the Mafia world.
Hey, don't run off without me.
Hold it!
It was you!
You killed my father!
Little punk, screw off!
Damn you!
Your old man was trash.
He knew the rules, but he didn't care.
He was a drug peddler.
Even women and children bought from him.
So I took him out.
What's going on?
Why can't I shoot?
I want to kill this guy, but
the stupid gun won't fire!
You called my papa trash!
But you're no better than he was!
Giorno would never have thought to describe
his silent defender with such a word.
In a bizarre twist of fate,
it was this lawbreaker,
this mafioso, who guided Giorno's
soul towards righteousness and virtue.
In a city replete with corrupt politicians
and unscrupulous police officers,
Giorno Giovanna found a reason to live.
He had no aspirations to become
a top Zero A soccer player.
He was to become a primo mafioso.
What a surprise.
That's the distinct tang of a liar.
You can call me Bruno Bucciarati.
Time for the truth.
We've already progressed
from questioning to torture.
It feels as if your head is about to
roll off your shoulders, doesn't it?
I suppose it's understandable
that you'd have no idea...
Why's a zipper embedded in my skin?
Giorno Giovanna, make no mistake.
If I wanted,
I could very easily roll your
head all over this funicular
while I force the name of Leaky
Eye Luca's attacker out of you.
If this guy gets off another attack,
I'll be nothing but a pile of body parts.
I've known about my powers for months now,
but this is the first time
I've ever had to seriously
consider using them to
attack another human being.
So far,
I know that a strike from Golden Wind can
breathe life into any inanimate object.
Whatever I target can be
turned into a living organism.
But what the hell is going to
happen if I hit an actual person?
I'll find out soon enough!
Time to come clean!
Giorno Giovanna!
Right!
It's now or never!
What?
So that's how it is.
You're a STAN user.
You could see my powers this whole time.
What did you just call me?
It's all adding up now.
You disgraced Leaky!
There's no way!
Golden Wind hit him dead on!
A blow that strong should have at
least Broken a few
of his bones
what
did
you just do you son of a bitch what
the hell i was barely standing a second
ago but now my body's brimming with
power i can feel the energy getting
stronger it's like some kind of life
stirring gasoline pulsing through my veins.
What?
It's like it's moving in slow motion.
Could his stand's punch have
left me in this heightened state?
A stand that supercharges your enemies.
What a foolish power.
Invigorate this, Jean Chobana!
What's this?
That's my body.
I'm standing behind myself, and
the handle's perfectly straight.
There's no way.
My mind's playing tricks on me, that's it.
I only thought I was moving with
some kind of extraordinary power.
But what if my body really has been
separated from my consciousness?
Miseria, I have to get out of the way!
Damn it!
Serene pain is creeping across my jaw!
Jean isn't moving in slow motion.
My consciousness is working in hyperdrive.
I see.
It seems that using golden
wind to flood a living person's
body with extra life force
ultimately leads to delirium,
at least of the senses.
I still don't know why I've been
granted these powers, but...
I think it would be a
waste not to use them.
Holy shit!
The hell are you guys doing?
Hey, I'm gonna call the cops!
Sorry for the commotion.
You have my word.
This fight won't involve
ordinary citizens.
There's no need to worry.
So this is the power of Giorno's stand.
Still,
it seems he doesn't have a
clear grasp of what a stand is,
which makes his prowess
all the more fearsome.
What do you know?
These stands of ours have a limited reach,
only a few meters from the look of things.
I thought you were some ordinary kid,
just an unaffiliated
fifteen-year-old shitheel.
But now I know better!
You're the one who
assaulted Leaky Eye Luca!
I wanna know why you did it.
The boss demands a straight answer!
I'm guessing it was an accident,
isn't what you want to hear?
And now that you've found me,
it's my turn to be eliminated?
Admit it.
You came fully prepared
to kill, didn't you?
You've got Executioner
written all over your face.
You boarded the car knowing that
you might be ending someone's life.
And an Executioner must always
stand ready to be executed.
This isn't a bluff.
I can feel the bloodlust in the air.
This little punk is
actually willing to kill me.
Despite his calm demeanor, he has a
savage side, which makes him dangerous!
Zipperman!
That must be this guy's stand.
Don't be a fool.
You must be aware that my
stand is the more powerful one.
Luckily, I'm not obligated
to return you alive.
So I'm good killing you here.
That said, I believe I've had my fill of
exposing myself to your strange talents.
If you'll excuse me.
Enjoy this reprieve.
I'll take you out when
you least expect it.
You're kidding me.
He could put a zipper on a
wall and pass right through it?
Katsu!
But things just got a lot
worse now that he's outside.
If I lose track of this freak show now,
it won't matter what I
can do with Golden Wind.
He'll be able to monitor my every move.
Losing sight of him means opening
myself up to be killed at any second.
I've got to catch him!
Worst case scenario is that he tells his
associates that I'm the
one who did Luca in.
There's no time to waste.
This game of cat and mouse ends here.
My future depends on it!
He's gone.
But I just saw him.
Wait, that zipper.
Can he use it to hide in people too?
How else could he have
disappeared so quickly?
That must have been what he
did with the fingers and I.
Bucciarati's hiding in someone.
He's wearing one of them like a costume.
And now he's going to
head deeper into the city.
I should probably go grab my bro.
Damn it.
They're scattering in all directions,
and there's not a zipper in sight.
Who is it?
Who is he hiding in?
Jeez!
Buss off, you pesky fly!
It's a tooth!
I used Golden Wind to
imbue your broken tooth
with life and turned it
into a common housefly.
The fly was compelled to return to
you, rendering your disguise useless.
Wonderful.
So much for saying I wouldn't
involve ordinary citizens.
Sorry, didn't mean to be a liar.
Then again,
you didn't suffer any more pain
than what you inflicted on that fly,
so it all evens out in
the end. Hang in there.
Giorno Giovanna, you've done very well.
It's clear that your
abilities demand respect.
I've no choice.
I shall face this fight head on.
Fool, you forced me to
eliminate you where you stand.
I refuse to let you get away.
I'll fight with my life to
keep you here. Oh, please.
I wouldn't concern myself with that.
I think if I were in your shoes,
I'd worry about what would happen?
after being zipped apart and
strewn across the ground.
Whichever one of us lands the
first blow will end up the victor.
Is something wrong?
Vieni, vieni, Giorno Giovanna!
Now say goodbye to your senses.
You're thinking why?
I struck him first.
I suppose it's only natural that'd
be running through your mind.
You lost because it's not my arm.
Fortunately, with my
stand's special ability,
I can conjoin objects to
virtually any part of my body.
So you know, this arm
belongs to that goon.
I made a quick exchange.
Given your stand's abilities,
I'm sure you can understand my wanting
to give myself some extra protection.
You can never be too careful.
Do you see now?
That's why your golden wind
was rendered ineffective.
It's too late now just give up
already this is the end for you.
Incredible he actually
tore off his own arm to
lengthen his range and
strike just a moment faster.
Golden wind do
it damn not again
he's forced my mind into
hyperdrive. Shit! I'm finished!
The destructive power of Giorno
Giovanna's stand may be negligible,
but that just makes
things much, much worse!
I've done it once, but to endure that
pain in slow motion over and over...
There's no question!
I'll die from the shock!
Don't...
Stop!
Why did you step out of range?
Wait, Giorno.
Explain yourself.
You had me.
Why did you stop?
Why didn't you kill me?
It's because you have a good soul.
You're in the Mafia, but you're decent.
Earlier, you went to attack
me, but hesitated a bit.
That's when I realized I
needed to stop my attack.
When you looked over at the
arm you stole from this kid,
the abnormal marks on his
skin caught you off guard,
which made you freeze up for a moment.
You didn't expect to see the arm
of an addict, and it shocked you.
I wonder how old he is.
Just 13.
Thing is, an ordinary mafiosa
wouldn't have been impeded.
If you were that type, I'd already
be ground into these stones by now.
You're different from the other goons.
Once I saw that, I didn't
see the need in us fighting.
Some here will even stoop
to selling drugs to kids.
Totally unforgivable.
Right?
I know that's how you feel.
But you've got a real big problem,
because your boss is the peddler.
The truth has you split down the middle.
That's why the side of the arm pains you.
You have a chivalrous heart.
What does my heart have
to do with anything?
Chivalrous or otherwise,
I still have to kill you.
My mission is to find
the person who took down
Luca and execute him like
the treacherous dog he is.
You didn't have the stomach
to go through with killing me.
But don't expect me to show
that detestable weakness! No.
Trust me, you just don't have
it in you to take my life.
Come again?
You won't kill me.
I'm sure of it.
How do you know?
Because you're going to be
joining me on my mission.
You see, I'm planning to beat your boss
and take back this city for the people.
What?
To rid this city of drug dealing
and child abusing mafiosi,
I have no other choice but
to become a mafioso myself.
What are you trying to say?
Surely your mission doesn't
involve joining our syndicate.
It's absurd.
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
Isn't it beautiful?
What something like that would entail?
Yeah, it's risky.
But to take back the city,
I have to join the syndicate that
controls it and work my way to the top.
Bucciarati, trust me.
I'll be a primo mafioso.
Get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
The freaky you is all I need.
I need your body.
Yeah, whatever you want.
I'll give it to you, baby.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got my mind.
You got my mind, I don't
want to do it for you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
To show how much
I'm gonna freak you?
What must I sell you?
What must I do?
To show how much I'm gonna freak you?
Thank you.